Munkhburen "Munduu" Munkhbileg

(405) 226-3998 • mmunkhbileg0711.github.io • mmunkhbileg9@ou.edu

SUMMARY STATEMENT

Data Scientist with strong math background and 3+ years of experience in developing ML models and processing and visualizing data to solve challenging business problems. Proficient in collaborating with teams of professionals for developing applications and solutions for business growth. Experienced in implementing Deep Learning and Machine Learning algorithms.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Tools & Languages: Python, Swift, Java, C#, ASP.NET MVC, R, SQL, MacOS, PowerBI, Tableau, Excel Packages: Pandas, Sklearn, Keras, TensorFlow, PyTorch, Spark, NumPy, Matplotlib, Statsmodels, Jupyter Notebook Statistics/Machine Learning: Supervised / Unsupervised Learning, Regularization, Reinforcement Learning, CNN, RNN

EDUCATION

University of Oklahoma - Norman, OK

Master of Science in Management Information Technology

Bachelor of Business Administration in Management Information System

UWC Atlantic College - Llantwit major, Wales, UK

International Baccalaureate Diploma

Expected December 2022

May 2018

RELEVANT COURSEWORK

Machine Learning Machine Learning Practice Deep Learning

Data Science and Analytics Business Data Analysis Database Design & Admin

PROJECTS

Stock Price Prediction

- Predicted Apple's stock with over 90% accuracy to enable informed investment
- Compared various machine learning algorithms (Autoregressive, LSTM, Arima)

Database Design and Implementation

- Designed ERD for Tire company
- Implemented and deployed using Microsoft SQL Server

Implement 20+ ML/DL algorithms from scratch

- Used Crime dataset for testing accuracy
- Visualized Testing Performances

WORK EXPERIENCE

Data Scientist/ Machine Learning Engineer, Interactive, Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia Biggest business analytics and solution company in Mongolia

June 2020 – August 2021 www.interactive.mn

May 2019 - September 2019

August 2019 – December 2019

Collaborated on a deep learning RNN project assisted with marketing and analysis

- Implemented ML algorithms and tools
- Performed statistical analysis on data set
- Tested machine learning models & improved models using results

TASO Construction - Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia

Product Manager Intern

- Learned to work with others to conduct research as part of the planning process
- Managed 30-person team to manufacture new product

Integrated Business Core Program, Price College of Business

Sales Manager, Inventory Manager

Manufactured sweater

- Sold over \$5000 and served 800 hours for local community
- Best seller of the company

CERTIFICATIONS

Data Scientist, The DataCamp Algorithm Expert, AlgoExpert Machine Learning Engineer, Educative January 2022 January 2022

December 2021